DEAR X
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
BUSAN INTERNATIONAL FILM FESTIVAL
Here comes actor Heo In-gang
on the red carpet.
He will be presenting
the Best Actor Award tonight
at the Busan International
Film Festival.
Please welcome him
with a big round of applause.
Take my hand.
Baek Ah-jin is now walking in
gracefully with Heo In-gang's escort.
As one of the most promising
next-generation stars
leading the future of Korean cinema
Baek Ah-jin captivates everyone
with poise and elegance
rarely seen in a rookie actor.
The two are walking down the carpet
dazzling under the camera flashes.
Please give them a warm welcome.
Hello, In-gang.
Hello.
You're the most coveted star in film
and advertising worldwide right now.
Everyone in the country is curious
to see just how far
your fame and success will go.
How does it feel?
It really sinks in
now that I'm here at the BIFF.
And here with superstar Heo In-gang
is Baek Ah-jin.
Hello, I'm Baek Ah-jin.
You must be nervous about being
on the red carpet for the first time.
Yes, I was very nervous
but thanks to In-gang's
advice and guidance
I've relaxed a little.
I think I'll be able
to enjoy the night
with a happy heart.
Then, you should stay
close by his side tonight.
But did you get permission from Lena?
Oh, Lena and I
are really close friends.
And she's a generous person
so I'm sure she'll understand.
Did I wake you?
Sorry.
I wanted to have a drink
with you tonight.
You're the best.
I told you to stop
coming to my place.
Then why didn't you change
the door code?
I know you don't mean it.
Oh, right.
Is this the hand that Ah-jin held?
I'll disinfect it for you.
Here we go.
It was Mi-ri's favor.
You mean Baek Ah-jin's favor.
Did you see the look in her eyes?
They're so creepy.
She acts innocent, polite,
and sweet to everyone
but I get chills
when I look into her eyes.
I can't tell
what emotions she's feeling.
Lena, how much longer
do I have to wait?
Wait for what?
About when I broke up with you?
You know I didn't mean that!
Why would you...
I've done this countless times.
Why won't you let it slide this time?
I thought I was being considerate
by waiting for you to accept it.
But maybe my kindness
gave you false hope.
Baby.
Baby, I'm sorry.
I'll be so lonely without you.
Can you give me one more chance?
I'll try harder.
It's all my fault. I'm sorry.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Bye.
Sleep tight.
Please help me.
What's going on?
Cut! Lena!
Director.
Her acting is completely off.
Hey, what's with that cheesy acting?
Didn't you rehearse it?
I'm sorry.
I wouldn't make that face
even if a cockroach were chasing me.
She's right, Ah-jin.
This isn't a difficult scene.
Hyang-i, get me a bottle of water.
I'm thirsty.
Just a moment.
Hey.
Go get it now.
But Ah-jin might catch a cold.
Now.
Okay.
Let's take five.
Take three!
Help.
Please help.
Take five!
- Ready.
- Take ten!
Please help me.
- Take 12!
- Take 15!
- Take 20!
- Please help.
This is nuts.
Are you glaring at me now?
Your eyes could cut steel.
Director, did you see
the look in her eyes?
How am I supposed to act
when she looks at me like that?
Lena!
Let's not make this harder, okay?
I can't get into character at all.
Can I just go home?
This is too much.
I've never seen anyone like her.
You know why
she's acting like that, right?
I suggest you just apologize
and smooth it over.
She's your senior, after all.
If we shut down this shoot today
we'll lose a fortune.
Please, I'm begging you.
I'm sorry, Director.
I'll do better.
We have zero chemistry.
I can't get into the scene with her.
Why does everyone act
like I'm doing it on purpose?
Why would I do that?
BAEK AH-JIN REPLACES LENA
FOR JIN SOJU
COSMETICS MARKET SLOWS,
YET THE BAEK AH-JIN EFFECT PERSISTS
A GUARANTEE OF SUCCESS?
Hey, In-gang, you're here.
Thanks for going
to the film festival with Ah-jin.
I helped you out,
so it's your turn now.
What is it?
You must know, but I broke up
with Lena a long time ago.
She couldn't accept it
and needed time to process
but this can't go on.
I need you to help end it.
In-gang.
The Hadere deal is almost signed.
Just wait a little longer.
Hadere requires
real couples as models.
No matter how much money's involved
I don't want to lie to the public.
I know how you feel.
I really do.
But could you think about it
once more?
I've done everything you asked.
But this time, I really can't.
All right, then.
I'm leaving.
Right.
Look after Ah-jin
during next week's shoot.
She's new and doesn't know much yet.
Treat her like family, okay?
Bye.
Hey.
Lena did what?
Do you think I'm a child?
Don't try to calm me down
with cheap candy.
Do you think
all I've got for you is candy?
Drunk driving.
Switching drivers afterward.
If that comes out,
your career is over.
Mi-ri!
Wait, I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Mi-ri, I was wrong.
Lena!
Please think.
Okay?
I knew she'd get what's coming.
Even if it's Ms. Seo
I still don't understand
how Lena acts that way.
There's always a reason.
Ms. Seo has been
in this industry for years.
This won't be her first time
handling someone as arrogant as Lena.
She prepares everything in advance.
Mi-ri, you can't just
leave like that.
Prepare for what?
I've heard about it.
She keeps a file that works
as shackles on every actor.
Stuff that could ruin
not just their careers
but also their lives if revealed.
You'd think it's a rumor
but when I look at Lena like that
- Mi-ri!
- it may not be a rumor.
Oh, jeez.
Mi-ri, please.
- She really asked for it.
- Gosh.
EPISODE 5: GRANT ME THE POWER
TO RISE TO THE TOP
Makeup looks great today.
Your face did it all, Ah-jin.
Oh, right.
We even go to the same salon.
We have so much in common.
One would think
we were a package deal.
You're even making me look bad.
Get me something to drink.
While you're at it,
give us the room for five minutes.
Sure.
I wonder why you irritate me so much.
Why do you think that is?
Well, I also wonder
why you absolutely despise me.
Rookie, you should be thinking
of a reason, not asking me.
You should very well know
the film festival pairing was
Ms. Seo's decision.
It wasn't something I could refuse--
And you wanted to refuse?
No.
I'd be a fool to refuse.
I had no reason to turn it down.
It was such a good opportunity.
Do you think you're untouchable
because Mi-ri is backing you?
Lena.
What dirt does she have on you
that makes you tremble like that?
Hyang-i turned herself in
and said it was her fault.
You're just here to give a statement,
so watch what you say.
Have a nice day.
I've been so curious
that I've lost sleep over this.
Would you tell me, too?
You.
Don't ask me for reasons.
Look for the reasons...
in yourself.
That's the only way
you won't be replaced next time.
Ah-jin, are you heading out?
My manager's waiting downstairs.
See you.
Bye.
That bitch.
Delivery.
If and when you become
more useful than you are now
I might have a use for you.
Then we could meet again.
Man.
I really missed you.
Hyang-i, you said
you used to be Lena's manager, right?
Yes.
Is that why she mistreats you?
Who knows what's in her head?
I thought I did my best.
Why do you ask?
Because you're my manager now.
Imagine how I'll feel
if anyone talks down to you.
Especially Lena.
She already hates me.
Maybe that's why
she takes it out on you.
If she ever does that again,
make sure to tell me, okay?
Don't worry.
Remember the shackle file
I mentioned last time?
I asked around, and they said
Ms. Seo keeps it in her desk drawer.
If things go south,
we can just take that.
Hyang-i.
We're the same age.
Why do you keep using the honorifics?
You can drop it when it's just us.
You sure?
YOON SEOK-HA'S FIRST BOOK SIGNING
CO-OFFENDER Y
A JOURNEY THROUGH STORIES
WITH AUTHOR YOON SEOK-HA
NUMBER 1 BESTSELLER FOR 7 WEEKS
WINNER OF THE 2021
LITERARY SQUARE NOVEL AWARD
Get out right now!
How dare you come here?
Father.
Do you think I'd come here
if I had any other choice?
Don't "Father" me!
I warned you not to jump
into a business you can't handle.
Now you took out loan-shark money?
Are you out of your mind?
Would I be here
if I were in my right mind?
Father.
I feel like I'm going to die.
People shouldn't have to die
over money.
Help me out this once--
You think I don't know you?
Get out
if you're here to spew nonsense.
I can't stand the sight of you.
Then I'll go to Jun-seo and beg him.
Is that what you want?
What did you say?
How dare you--
It's not like you can take
that money with you when you die!
Let's be honest.
I'm his mother.
I have the right to ask him for this.
I raised your precious grandson
with these hands!
I raised the child that you dote on
but you won't spare a single penny
for the daughter-in-law?
Does that make sense?
Soo-hyuk, get her out now.
Ma'am, let's go.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Calm down.
- Get off me.
- This way.
- You can't do this to me.
You'll be punished for this!
Let go of me!
Father!
How long has she been coming here?
It's none of your concern.
Is this all the books you brought?
This won't even cover
a fraction of my contacts.
Next time, bring a whole bundle.
NAMYEONG BANK
I gave you my account number.
Do you have to show up at the house?
You know your uncle will flip
if he finds out.
- Auntie, I just--
- Sure.
I get that you want to help
your little brother.
I won't stop you from doing that.
But put yourself in his shoes.
Who would want to see a brother
who killed their own dad?
Why do you have to make me
say these things?
I get it, so don't worry.
I'll transfer the money next time.
Auntie.
You'll keep sending me
Jae-hun's photos, right?
I heard he's doing
great in school, unlike me.
If he wins any awards
or gets good grades, send them to me.
Thank you
for not abandoning him
and raising him well.
And I'm sorry.
I'll spend the rest of my life
making it up to you.
So, don't cry over being harsh to me.
Just be happy.
Okay?
Auntie, I'm home.
Hello, please take
good care of In-gang.
- Thank you.
- Grab some snacks.
Isn't he amazing?
Please take good care of him.
- Thanks for the snacks.
- Sure.
- Help yourselves.
- Thank you.
Hi!
Have some coffee.
- It's on me today.
- Thank you so much.
You know the publishing industry
has been rough these days.
But your book is bucking the trend.
We'll need aggressive promo
to keep the momentum
and we'll need your help.
I'll do whatever I can to help.
Great.
I'll green-light
the booking requests, then.
Sure.
We're moving in one minute.
Get ready, everyone.
It's gotten busy here
with that drama shoot.
You must come here often
to have picked this place.
Sorry for the hassle.
No, I picked it on purpose.
I wanted to take a look.
Oh, is it for your next book?
Then the TV promo will help
with your writing.
I think so.
- Shall we head out?
- Yes.
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
No, it's fine.
- Director, I'm here.
- Was traffic bad?
Parking took forever.
Did you wait long?
Look.
We need to talk.
Let's talk outside.
Cut!
One more time.
- Gather up!
- Everyone, gather!
Quickly!
That was great,
but we need more movement.
Jun-seo.
I finally tracked you down
and you're still clinging to Ah-jin,
who treats you less than a rat?
You're pathetic!
"Still"?
So, there was something
between him and Baek Ah-jin before?
Get off me.
When did you get back?
When you get back,
you call your mother first.
Do I have to find out
from your advertisement?
Why is it so hard
to see my own son's face?
Did you keep your promise to me?
What promise?
To apologize to Ah-jin.
How long are you going to pretend
nothing happened?
She ended up miserable,
all because of you.
I can barely stand
to look at you.
Lena.
What are you doing here?
Introduce me to this author.
Sorry?
I'll post on Instagram and everywhere
that I loved his book.
I don't care
if it's on TV or the radio.
We can tell them to make a segment
like "Meet the Author."
Why the sudden interest?
My soju deal is gone
so I can hand back
the "Korea's Little Sister" title.
I think it's time to rebrand
as sophisticated and intellectual.
So, are you doing it or not?
This is your job.
I'll make some calls now.
I am Ah-jin's mother.
You still need to call ahead--
What mother calls ahead?
- You can't just barge in--
- Quiet.
- Where's the CEO's office?
- What?
Ah-jin's mother?
As far as I know,
her mother passed away.
I guess she hasn't told you.
I was her stepmother,
but I raised her with love.
I fed her well
and gave her a good bed
as if she were my own child.
Yes, I heard.
You lovingly raised her
and threw her out.
She said that?
She left on her own.
Why are you here?
Keep her off TV.
Let me live.
You know that's impossible.
What do you really want?
Money?
I have money.
Hello.
Ah-jin.
Your mother is here.
Her, an actress?
Don't make me laugh.
She's not the type to wear
nice clothes and soak up applause.
She's lowborn by nature.
An alcoholic for a mother
and a criminal for a father.
What more do you need to know?
Excuse me?
Do you know how her father died?
He was killed.
Someone else served time,
but I know the truth.
Ah-jin did it.
Just thinking about it
makes my heart race
and terrifies me.
And now, she's on TV everywhere
so I'm too scared
to even breathe.
It's best you stay away
from that bitch.
Ignore me if you want
but you'll see what I mean
once she devours you.
Most people only get it
after she's taken an arm
because of how cunning she is.
Long time no see.
How have you been?
Great, thanks to you.
Since you beat me everywhere
but the face to put me on camera.
Why are you here?
I'm not here to see you.
I came so I won't have to see you
ever again.
I hope you get my drift.
Let's not meet again.
Sorry about that.
That must have been unpleasant.
It wasn't fun, but I'm used to it.
It's also my job
to handle these things.
And it's the reason
you need to earn well.
I understand.
I'll climb steadily
so this doesn't happen again.
What kind of life have you lived?
Even your own mother
isn't on your side.
Your past must be fascinating.
I'm dying to know.
If you keep this up
you'll only end up more upset.
- Are you worried for me?
- Yes.
Because I want you to keep working
in this field for a long time.
Worry about yourself.
I'm busy figuring out
what'll finally make me feel better.
Look forward to it.
SPECIAL GUESTS
AUTHOR YOON SEOK-HA, ACTRESS LENA
Hey, Lena.
This is the author
you'll be appearing with. Say hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleasure to meet you.
You're really handsome for an author.
Thank you.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Or you had one?
Someone you can't get over?
I'm joking.
Do you want to grab dinner after?
No, thank you.
We'll bring you both in together
in five minutes.
CO-OFFENDER Y
"'Let me find the highest place.
Let every moment become a chance
to paint myself.
And let my finished portrait hang
at the very top of the world.'
This was her prayer
and I prayed it wouldn't be answered.
I prayed that the child
I failed to save
somehow escaped the savagery
and now rests in quiet days."
Okay, I got it.
Ah-jin, you must be hungry.
- Who was that on the phone?
- The agency.
There will be
a building inspection today.
Power's out from six o'clock,
so everyone's heading home early.
Great work, everyone.
- Great work.
- Thank you.
You two were fantastic.
- The live reactions were amazing.
- That's great.
- See you next time.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
If dinner's a no, do you like drinks?
- Hong-sik.
- Yes?
He's taking me home tonight,
so you can clock out first.
Okay.
I can't drive.
Be my chauffeur.
Are you bored, or just naturally--
Naturally a psycho?
Think whatever you want.
I'll wait on the first floor.
Hyang-i.
You must be tired.
Don't you have to take the car back
to the office after you drop me off?
You know what?
Just let me off there,
then go straight home.
It's fine. I'm okay.
And if I drop you off at the office,
how will you get home?
That's what taxis are for.
You said everyone left early, anyway.
You should go home and get some rest.
Should I?
HYANG-I
I'LL TELL HER
THE BUILDING WILL BE UNDER INSPECTION
Actually
I should swing by the office.
I left something really important.
Mind if I go grab it?
I'm scared someone might take it.
Power's out from six o'clock,
so everyone's heading home early.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
Looking for this?
BAEK AH-JIN MATERIALS
KANG LENA MATERIALS
Or this one?
Wow, you're sweating.
Did you walk all the way up here?
The central elevator runs
even in emergencies.
I guess you didn't know.
Anyway, thanks to that,
I beat you here.
Now, they're both in my hands.
Lena.
Lena!
You.
Were you going to use these
to bring me down?
Hate to break it to you,
but you're the one who's screwed now.
Should we see
who really gets screwed?
Get on your knees and beg.
"Lena
spare me.
I'm sorry."
Do it.
Easy, right?
It costs no money or effort
as long as you swallow your pride.
I guess you're not desperate yet.
You want to keep your pride?
Then, how about this?
No wonder In-gang is fed up with you.
This fucking bitch.
What did you say?
This psycho.
Let's go.
No need to be alarmed.
It was just a senior giving
an arrogant junior a lesson.
You call that a lesson?
Are you a Baek Ah-jin fan?
You seem oddly concerned.
Even if I weren't,
it wasn't normal behavior.
It sounds like you know her.
Do you know how insane she is?
She screwed me over
every chance she got.
But today
I won.
Are you sure you won?
You bet.
I feel great.
What are you doing on Christmas Eve?
It's our agency's anniversary.
Come with me.
Why should I?
Actually, my ex is going.
I want to make him jealous
and win him back.
Help me out.
And Ah-jin will be there.
CO-OFFENDER Y
I like being in the spotlight.
But I also love observing people.
Using and sharing emotions
is very fascinating.
And I think I have a gift for it.
What do I treasure most? Myself.
I want to be a chameleon-like actress
who can turn into any color.
Hello.
- Ms. Seo!
- Hi!
- Hello.
- Congrats.
Thank you for coming.
We will now begin
Longstar Entertainment's
Seventh Founding Anniversary
and the 2021 Year-End Party.
First, greetings
from CEO Seo Mi-ri and our guests.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Congratulations.
- I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Hello, I'm Seo Mi-ri,
the CEO of Longstar Entertainment.
The year's already over.
Looking back
every single moment...
You take this without water?
Thank you for hanging in there
so well this year.
To everyone who's here...
Ah-jin.
Did you get home safely that day?
It was a bit of discipline
from senior to junior
so don't take it personally.
Don't worry, Lena.
Say hi.
He's the hottest name
in publishing now.
This is Yoon Seok-ha.
Come on. Say hello.
Hello.
I'm Yoon Seok-ha.
And this is my junior actress,
Baek Ah-jin.
Nice to meet you.
This isn't your first meeting, right?
You saw each other last time.
In the parking lot.
Thanks for earlier.
Next up is a video reel
featuring seven years of Longstar's
growth through joys and sorrows.
Let's watch it together.
You're ignoring me.
If you had basic human decency
you wouldn't.
What else do you want me to do?
I told you I had no choice.
Lena.
Lena!
Should we see
who really gets screwed?
Get on your knees and beg.
Turn it off.
It was so realistic
that I almost thought it was real.
You must be startled.
This is how dedicated our actors are.
Please give them a big hand!
- Hyang-i.
- Yes?
What about after you get off work?
Will you report to Lena?
That shackle file in Ms. Seo's desk.
Did Lena ask you to tell me about it?
Ah-jin, how did you--
Exactly which parts
did she tell you to say?
I swear I didn't want to.
I honestly didn't want to do it.
But she loaned us money when my dad
had stomach cancer surgery
and threatened me to pay it back.
So, I'm supposed to go through
Ms. Seo's desk to find the file?
That's what she wants, right?
I'm on your side.
You know I'm nothing like her.
If you're really sorry
you start helping me now.
I fell into her trap
and you moved the way she told you.
Wasn't it fun?
I thought it was.
What?
"Superstar Lena Gets Caught
Assaulting a Rookie."
That can be the title.
If this video gets out
the public will go wild.
Massive reputation damage,
commercial penalty fees
a lifetime of hate,
mockery, and insults...
- What else?
- Hey.
If you don't want that
how about you kneel and beg?
Get on your knees and beg.
"Lena."
"Ah-jin
I'm sorry."
"Spare me."
Say it.
You said it was easy.
It costs no money or effort.
Easy, right?
It costs no money or effort
as long as you swallow your pride.
As long as you swallow your pride.
Listen.
You should see the look on your face.
I'm kidding, Lena.
As long as you don't bother me
I've got no reason
to post that video.
Let's get along from here on out.
Would you like one?
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
I always repay what I'm given.
I've been wondering
how to pay you back.
And look where you are.
Perfect to get knocked off.
Ms. Baek Ah-jin.
I'll do everything
to convict you of this murder.
Plenty of people here would love
to know your little secret.
Get out.
Have you checked in
on Choi Jung-ho lately?
You already forgot? He's the guy
whose life you fucked up.
A baseball bat to your dad's head.
Ah-jin.
We need to wrap up. Come over here.
NEWSHOUND HEE-KOOK
CHECK THIS PERSON OUT
Hey, Hee-kook.
Baek Ah-jin looks like she got caught
and is being blackmailed.
Look into it.
Yes, she seemed to know the guy.
I'd like to thank Ms. Seo,
who believed in me
and to our agency family
as well as the senior actors.
I'll work even harder.
To Longstar Entertainment's
boundless growth!
- Cheers!
It's cold.
I'll get you something warm.
CO-OFFENDER Y
My misfortune
turned into your commodity.
I PRAYED THAT THE CHILD I FAILED
TO SAVE SOMEHOW ESCAPED THE SAVAGERY
You really missed me, didn't you?
It hurt...
a lot.
Of course, it did.
It also hurt me a lot.
I thought you'd be at ease by now.
I've always suffered.
I thought I had escaped
but I was always in the same place.
I'm sick of it.
Jun-seo.
Help me.
I want to learn to love him.
Heo In-gang.
DEAR X
Subtitles by Ho-young Yun